searchqu.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Searchnu.com takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about Searchnu.com's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how Searchnu.com receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at searchnu.com (the "Site"). 

## Collection and Use of Information 

Searchnu.com does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). Searchnu.com may request that a user provide an e-mail address if such user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters and service related announcements. If a user provides an e-mail address to Searchnu.com, such user authorizes Searchnu.com to send user communications. 

Searchnu.com may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at Searchnu.com's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. Searchnu.com's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information. 

Searchnu.com may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. Searchnu.com collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. Searchnu.com will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

## Sharing and Disclosure of Information

Searchnu.com does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. Searchnu.com may disclose your Personal Information if Searchnu.com believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on Searchnu.com; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Searchnu.com (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Searchnu.com services or members of the public.

## Security

Searchnu.com takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although Searchnu.com cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, Searchnu.com has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. 

## Business Transitions

In the event that Searchnu.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. Searchnu.com will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information Searchnu.com may have prior to such transfer.

## Changes to Policy

From time to time, Searchnu.com may revise this Policy. Searchnu.com will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information Searchnu.com collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed. 

## Change or Removal of Information

If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@searchnu.com](mailto:support@searchnu.com) with the request or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

If a user no longer wishes to receive e-mail communication from Searchnu.com, such as offers, updates and newsletters, a user may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. In addition, a user can remove their e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of OPT-OUT to [support@searchnu.com](mailto:support@searchnu.com)

## Contact Information

Searchnu.com is owned and operated by Bandoo Media Inc. Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to [privacy@searchnu.com](mailto:privacy@searchnu.com) or by writing to Bandoo Media Inc., Attention: Privacy Policy Administrator, 40 kimonos st.3095 Limassol, Cyprus
